triberr.com 2019-06-24

# Triberr Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us. This Privacy Policy applies to all of the products, widgets, services and websites offered by Triberr Inc. or its subsidiaries or affiliated companies ; collectively, Triberr's "services".

Registration with, use of, and access to the Service is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use located at https://triberr.com/terms-of-service. 

In order to provide our full range of services, we may collect the following types of information listed below.

### Personal Information We May Collect

For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, “Personal Information” means any information relating to an identified or identifiable individual. We obtain Personal Information relating to you from various sources described below. Where applicable, we indicate whether and why you must provide us with your Personal Information, as well as the consequences of failing to do so. If you do not provide Personal Information when requested, you may not be able to benefit from our Service if that information is necessary to provide you with the service or if we are legally required to collect it.

### Information You Provide

When you sign up for Triberr or other Triberr service or promotion that requires registration, we ask you for personal information (such as your name, email address and an account password). We may combine the information you submit under your account with information from other Triberr services or third parties in order to provide you with a better experience and to improve the quality of our services.

#### **Personal Information Collected From Authenticated Social Media Accounts.**

For the purposes of this section ‘authentication’ describes the action of a user connecting and authorization of a social media account(s) with his / her / their Triberr account. Only the person authorized can connect and disconnect his or her social media account(s). 

If you connect a social media account to your Triberr account we may collect certain information stored in your social media account. 

#### **When a Facebook Account is Connected**

Triberr may allow you to connect a Facebook page or profile to your Triberr account, in which case we will access certain information from Triberr regarding your account. In particular, we may collect profile image, display name, username or page ID or profile ID, access tokens, gender, age, location, sent posts. This includes the content of your post and engagement data (such as click rates, likes, re-shares, impressions, as well as general engagement counts), to the extent permitted by applicable law. This data will only be used by Triberr to provide you with the Service you expect and will not be shared with any third parties.

#### **When a Twitter Account is Connected**

Triberr may allow you to connect a Twitter profile to your Triberr account, in which case we will access certain information from Twitter regarding your account. In particular, we may collect your profile image, display name, username or profile ID, location, sex, follower count, following count, tweet count, access tokens, and sent posts. This includes the content of your post and engagement data (such as click rates, likes, retweets, re-shares, impressions, as well as general engagement counts) to the extent permitted by applicable law. This data will only be used by Triberr to provide you with the Service you expect and will not be shared with any third parties.

#### **When a Linkedin Account is Connected**

Triberr may allow you to connect a LinkedIn profile to your Triberr account, in which case we will access certain information from LinkedIn regarding your account. In particular, we may collect profile image, display name, username or profile ID, network count, bio, headline description, access tokens, and sent posts. This includes the content of your post and engagement data (such as click rates, likes, re-shares, impressions, as well as general engagement counts), to the extent permitted by applicable law. This data will only be used by Triberr to provide you with the Service you expect and will not be shared with any third parties.

#### **When a YouTube Account is Connected**

Triberr may allow you to connect a Youtube channel to your Triberr account, in which case we will access certain information from Youtube regarding your account. In particular, we may collect profile image, display name, username or profile ID, access tokens, and sent posts. This includes the content of your post and engagement data (such as click rates, likes, re-shares, impressions, as well as general engagement counts), to the extent permitted by applicable law. This data will only be used by Triberr to provide you with the Service you expect and will not be shared with any third parties.

### Personal Information Automatically Obtained from Your Interactions with the Service

#### **Cookies**

When you visit Triberr, we send one or more cookies – a small file containing a string of characters – to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing user preferences and tracking user trends. We may set a cookie in your browser when you visit a website and view or click on an ad supported by Triberr's advertising services.

#### **Log Information**

When you access Triberr services, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit our website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

#### **User Communications**

When you send messages, chats, or other communications to Triberr, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services.

#### **Affiliated Sites**

We offer some of our services in connection with other web sites. Personal information that you provide to those sites may be sent to Triberr in order to deliver the service. We process such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. The affiliated sites may have different privacy practices and we encourage you to read their privacy policies.

#### **Other Sites**

This Privacy Policy applies to Triberr services only. We do not exercise control over the sites which display widgets or services from Triberr. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you.

Triberr only processes personal information for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy and/or the supplementary privacy notices for specific services. In addition to the above, such purposes include:

  * Providing our services to users, including the display of customized content and advertising;
  * Auditing, research and analysis in order to maintain, protect and improve our services;
  * Ensuring the technical functioning of our network; and
  * Developing new services.

Triberr processes personal information on our servers in the United States of America. In some cases, we process personal information on a server outside your own country. We may process personal information to provide our own services. In some cases, we may process personal information on behalf of and according to the instructions of a third party, such as our advertising partners.

#### **Choices for Personal Information**

When you register at Triberr, we ask you to provide personal information. If we use this information in a manner different than the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for your consent prior to such use.

If we propose to use personal information for any purposes other than those described in this Privacy Policy and/or in the specific service privacy notices, we will offer you an effective way to opt out of the use of personal information for those other purposes. We will not collect or use sensitive information for purposes other than those described in this Privacy Policy and/or in the supplementary service privacy notices, unless we have obtained your prior consent.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some Triberr features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.

You can decline to submit personal information to any of our services, in which case Triberr may not be able to provide those services to you.

If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such marketing communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications. You may also opt out from receiving commercial email from us by sending your request to us by email at [support@triberr.com](mailto:support@triberr.com). Please be aware that, even after you opt out from receiving commercial messages from us, you may continue to receive administrative messages from us regarding the Service.

In certain jurisdictions you have the right to request access and receive information about the Personal Information we maintain about you, to update and correct inaccuracies in your Personal Information, to restrict or object to the processing of your Personal Information, to have the information blocked, anonymized or deleted, as appropriate, or to exercise your right to data portability to transfer your Personal Information to another company. Those rights may be limited in some circumstances by local law requirements. In addition to the above-mentioned rights, you also have the right to lodge a complaint with a competent supervisory authority subject to applicable law.

Where required by law, we obtain your consent for the processing of certain Personal Information collected by cookies or similar technologies, or used to send you direct marketing communications, or when we carry out other processing activities for which consent may be required. If we rely on consent for the processing of your Personal Information, you have the right to withdraw it at any time and free of charge. When you do so, this will not affect the lawfulness of the processing before your consent withdrawal.

To update your preferences, ask us to remove your information from our mailing lists, delete your account or submit a request to exercise your rights under applicable law, please contact us at [support@triberr.com](mailto:support@triberr.com)

#### **How We May Use Your Personal Information**

We may use the Personal Information we obtain about you to:

  * create and manage your account, provide our Service, process payments, and respond to your inquiries;
  * manage account authentication
  * communicate with you to verify your account and for informational and operational purposes, such as account management, customer service, or system maintenance, including periodically emailing you service-related announcements;
  * tailor our Service (e.g., we may use cookies and similar technologies to remember your preferences);
  * publish your content, comments or messages on social media platforms;
  * provide tailored advertising, for Triberr services, via Google AdWords;
  * aggregate your Personal Information for analytical purposes;
  * provide customer support;
  * operate, evaluate and improve our business (including by developing new products and services; managing our communications; determining the effectiveness of our advertising; analyzing how the Service is being accessed and used; tracking performance of the Service; debugging the Service; facilitating the use of our Service);
  * send you marketing communications about products, services, offers, programs and promotions of Triberr, and affiliated companies;
  * ensure the security of our Service;
  * manage our customer, service provider and partner relationships;
  * enforce our agreements related to our Service and our other legal rights; and
  * comply with applicable legal requirements, industry standards and our policies.

If you are located in the European Economic Area, we may process your Personal Information for the above purposes when:

  * you have consented to the use of your Personal Information, For example, we may seek to obtain your consent for our uses of cookies or similar technologies, or to send you marketing communications.
  * we need your Personal Information to provide you with services and products requested by you, or to respond to your inquiries,
  * we have a legal obligation to use your Personal Information, or
  * we have a legitimate interest in using your Personal Information. In particular, we have a legitimate interest in using your Personal Information to ensure and improve the safety, security, and performance of our Service, to anonymize Personal Information and carry out data analyses.

### How We Share Your Personal Information

Triberr only shares personal information with other companies or individuals outside of Triberr in the following limited circumstances:

  * We have your consent. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information.
  * We provide such information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.
  * We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of Triberr, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.
  * If Triberr becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.
  * We may share with third parties certain pieces of aggregated, non-personal information, such as the number of users who clicked on a particular term. Such information does not identify you individually.
  * Social Media Platforms - Our primary purpose for using information is to publish your content on social platforms, allow you to track metrics for analytical purposes, and engage with customers through public replies and conversations (direct messages or “DMs”). We may allow you to link your account on Triberr with an account on a third party social network platform, such as Twitter, Facebook, Linkedin, Youtube, or Gmail, and to transfer your information to and from the applicable third party platform. Once you share your content to a social media platform, its use will be governed by that platform’s privacy policy.
  * Service Providers - We engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to us, including hosting and maintenance, error monitoring, debugging, performance monitoring, billing, customer relationship, database storage and management, and direct marketing campaigns. We may share your Personal Information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services. We also require these third parties to maintain the privacy and security of the Personal Information they process on our behalf.
  * Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement - Triberr cooperates with government and law enforcement officials or private parties to enforce and comply with the law. To the extent permitted under applicable law, we may disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we believe is necessary or appropriate to investigate, respond to, and defend against claims, for legal process (including subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of Triberr or a third party, to protect Triberr against liability, for the safety of the public or any person, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, fraudulent, abusive, or legally actionable activity, to protect the security or integrity of the Service and any equipment used to make the Service available, or to comply with the law.
  * Business Transfers - Triberr may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including Personal Information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization, sale of assets, or similar transaction, or in the event of insolvency or bankruptcy. You will have the opportunity to opt out of any such transfer if the new entity’s planned processing of your information differs materially from that set forth in this Privacy Policy.
  * Other Third Parties - We may share Personal Information with our headquarters, sister sites, and or affiliates, and business partners to whom it is reasonably necessary or desirable for us to disclose your data for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. We may also make certain non-Personal Information available to third parties for various purposes, including for business or marketing purposes or to assist third parties in understanding our users’ interest, habits, and usage patterns for certain programs, content, services, advertisements, promotions, and functionality available through the Service.

### Information Security

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data.

We restrict access to personal information to Triberr employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

### Data Integrity

Triberr processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Privacy Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy notice. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary.

### Accessing and Updating Personal Information

When you use Triberr services, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes), or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort. Some of our services have different procedures to access, correct or delete users' personal information. We provide the details for these procedures in the specific privacy notices or FAQs for these services.

### Data Transfers

Triberr is based in the United States. Personal Information that we collect may be transferred to, and stored at, any of our affiliates, partners or service providers which may be inside or outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”) and Switzerland, including the United States. By submitting your personal data, you agree to such transfers. Your Personal Information may be transferred to countries that do not have the same data protection laws as the country in which you initially provided the information. When we transfer or disclose your Personal Information to other countries, we will protect that information as described in this Privacy Policy.

### Child Privacy

The Site is not directed to persons under 18. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Information without their consent, he or she should contact us at [support@triberr.com](mailto:support@triberr.com) We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under 18. If we become aware that a child under 18 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our files.

### Enforcement

Triberr regularly reviews its compliance with this Privacy Policy. Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy or Triberr's treatment of personal information by contacting us through this web site.

When we receive formal written complaints, it is Triberr's policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between Triberr and an individual.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Privacy Policy changes). Each version of this Privacy Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its effective date.

### How to Contact Us

Triberr is the entity responsible for the processing of your Personal Information. If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, or if you would like to exercise your rights to your Personal Information, you may contact us by emailing us at [support@triberr.com](mailto:support@triberr.com)

Last Updated on June 28, 2018.
